Transcript and translation
from Definitegj http://youtu.be/VwwEV6RqHZ0
Sung by 林芯儀 (Shennio Lin)
The snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
白雪纷飞一片银色世界
Bái xuě fēn fēi yī piàn yín sè shì jiè
A silvery-white world with the flurrying snow
not a footprint to be seen
放眼望去是沉寂
Fàng yǎn wàng qù shì chén jì
Greeted with solitary silence
A kingdom of isolation,
遥远国度放逐自我
Yáo yuǎn guó dù fàng zhú zì wǒ
I have exiled the distant kingdom
and it looks like I'm the queen
孤单寂寞每一天
Gū dān jì mò měi yī tiān
that made me lonely, every day
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
思绪像狂风呼啸 巨浪般澎湃
Sī xù xiàng kuáng fēng hū xiào Jù làng bān péngpài
My thoughts are swirling like the raging waves in a storm
Couldn't keep it in, heaven knows I tried
无法再压抑 最后的忍耐
Wú fǎ zài yā yì zuì hòu de rěn nài
Couldn't suppress it, end of my endurance.
Don't let them in, don't let them see
不要靠近不要相信
Bù yào kào jìn bù yào xiāng xìn
Do not get close and do not trust
Be the good girl you always had to be
乖乖听话安分一如往昔
Guāi guāi tīng huà ān fèn yī rú wǎng xī
Be the good girl you always have to be
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
隐藏坚强 拒绝表露
Yǐn cáng jiān qiáng jù jué biǎo lù
Conceal, be strong. Do not reveal.
Well, now they know!
抛下所有
Pāo xià suǒ yǒu
Abandon it all!
Let it go, let it go!
放开手 放开手
Fàng kāi shǒu Fàng kāi shǒu
Let go, let go!
Can't hold it back any more!
不需要任何理由
Bù xū yào rèn hé lǐ yóu
Don't need reason any more
Let it go, let it go!
放开手 放开手
Fàng kāi shǒu Fàng kāi shǒu
Let go, let go!
Turn away and slam the door!
不理会心中枷锁
Bù lǐ huì xīn zhōng jiā suǒ
Ignore shackles that chained the heart
I don't care what they're going to say
还以为 曾经在乎过谁
Hái yǐ wéi Céng jīng zài hū guò shuí
I once thought that I care for them
Let the storm rage on
让暴雨翻腾
Ràng bào yǔ fān téng
Let the storm rage on
The cold never bothered me anyway.
从不畏惧臣服冰霜风雪
Cóng bù wèi jù chén fú bīng shuāng fēng xuě
I've never been afraid of the ice and snow.
It's funny how some distance
你我之间有距离
Nǐ wǒ zhī jiān yǒu jù lí
The distance between you and me
Makes everything seem small
一切变得渺小
yī qiè biàn dé miǎo xiǎo
Makes everything seem small
And the fears that once controlled me
那萦绕心头的恐惧
Nà yíng rào xīn tóu de kǒng jù
And the fear that once controlled me
Can't get to me at all!
已经不再重要
Yǐ jīng bù zài zhòng yào
Is no longer important!
It's time to see what I can do
看看我要 如何去做
Kàn kàn wǒ yào rú hé qù zuò
Watch me, let's see what I can do
To test the limits and break through
测试极限 能否突破
Cè shì jí xiàn néng fǒu tú pò
To test the limits and break through
No right, no wrong, no rules for me
没有对错 没有束缚
Méi yǒu duì cuò Méi yǒu shù fù
No right, no wrong, no more restraints
I'm free!
起飞
Qǐ fēi
Take off!
Let it go, let it go!
放开手 放开手
Fàng kāi shǒu Fàng kāi shǒu
Let go, let go!
I am one with the wind and sky
从今往后有我主宰
Cóng jīn wǎng hòu yǒu wǒ zhǔ zǎi
I'll make my own calls from now on
Let it go, let it go!
让它走 让它走
Ràng tā zǒu ràng tā zǒu
Let it leave, let it leave!
You'll never see me cry
绝不再受伤害
Jué bù zài shòu shāng hài
Never be hurt again
Here I stand, and here I'll stay,
新世界 在我眼前
Xīn shì jiè Zài wǒ yǎn qián
Brand new world, right ahead of me
Let the storm rage on...
让暴雨翻腾
Ràng bào yǔ fān téng
Let the storm rage on...
My power flurries through the air and to the ground
力量强大 从地底直窜上云霄
Lì liàng qiáng dà cóng dì dǐ zhí cuàn shàng yún xiāo
Great power soars through the clouds from the ground
My soul is spiralling in frozen fractals all around
我的心层层冰封 锐利碎片很难消
Wǒ de xīn céng céng bīng fēng ruì lì suì piàn hěn nán xiāo
My heart, layered with spiky ice, is difficult to thaw
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
心念动冰晶立起 天地将改变
Xīn niàn dòng bīng jīng lì qǐ tiān dì jiāng gǎi biàn
And one thought crystallizes, transforming the world
I'm never going back
前方的路等待
Qián fāng de lù děng dài
The future awaits me
The past is in the past!
过去不要留恋
Guò qù bù yào liú liàn
Don't linger in the past!
Let it go, let it go!
让它走 让它走
Ràng tā zǒu Ràng tā zǒu
Let it leave, let it leave!
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
乌云后面就是曙光
Wū yún hòu miàn jiù shì shǔ guāng
Every cloud has a silver lining
Let it go, let it go!
让它走 让它走
Ràng tā zǒu Ràng tā zǒu
Let it leave, let it leave!
That perfect girl is gone
只剩记忆回荡
Zhǐ shèng jì yì huí dàng
Only memories remain
Here I stand in the light of day
新世界 希望在眼前
Xīn shì jiè Xī wàng zài yǎn qián
Brand new world with bright prospect
Let the storm rage on!
让暴雨翻腾
Ràng bào yǔ fān téng
Let the storm rage on!
The cold never bothered me anyway.
从不畏惧臣服冰霜风雪
Cóng bù wèi jù chén fú bīng shuāng fēng xuě
I've never been afraid of the ice and snow.